

DUAA CHUNDRIGAR Laravel, Vue.js & Graphics Designer

About Me

As Developer

I am PHP, Laravel Web developer. I am highly skilled with PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, VueJs, Tailwind CSS, HTML, and CSS.

I am very passionate and dedicated to my work. I enjoy every step to the software development process from discussion and collaboration to concept and execution. More importantly I am most satisfied when I deliver the final product as per users requirements.

As Graphics Designer

I based my entire graphic design career around it! I have worked for a restaurant and franchises to create logos, brochures, menus, product labels and countless other deliverables. I can promise you I know what good food looks like. As someone who has a graphic design background, I can also promise you that I know how to market it.

Education

Jan 2018 - Current

BSIT (BS in Information Technology): Technology-based

HIAST - Autobhan Road Hyderabad

Work History

Web developer at Upwork 2021 - Present

Graphics Designer at Pizza Mama December 2021 - March 2022

Graphics Designer at Buzz Me February 2021 - March 2021

Graphics Designer at Nuha's Healthy Living October 2020 - Present

Skills

Github

PHP Laravel Javascript (vue.js) SQL Adobe Illustrator Figma Adobe Photoshop MS OFFICE

Contact

Address Hyderabad, 71000

Phone 923402486495

Email abdullahduaa85@gmail.com

Github https://github.com/DuaaChundrigar

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/duaa -chundrigar-365244